

CV Website

CONTACTS



+38 098-46-25-714

+38 050-471-60-06



martmarchmartmarch@gmail.com



https://www.linkedin.com/in/ oleksii-hiriavenko/



https://github.com/AlexHiriavenko/

PRO.SKILLS

HTML, CSS, SCSS, Bootstrap

JavaScript

NodeJs (basics)

React, Redux (Thunk, Toolkit), MUI, etc

Git, GitLab, GitHub

Gulp, Webpack, Vite

Swagger, Postman, Vercel, Netlify, Heroku

Figma, Trello

English

B1 - Intermediate (certificate)

EDUCATION

10.2022 - 09.2023

FRONTEND

DAN.IT Education (certificate)

2022 - 2023

COURSES

EPAM: frontend self paced online program

RS-School: Frontend, Nodejs basics

Udemy: React, Redux (by M.Nepomnyaschiy)

Udemy: TypeScript (in progress)

2002 - 2007

PROCESSING EQUIPMENT ENGINEER

Specialist (diploma)

Donetsk National University of Economics and Trade

CERTIFICATES

Oleksiy Hiryavenko

Frontend Developer

SUMMARY

A switcher with many years of experience in marketing and purchasing management, passionate about front-end and programming in general. Participant of the IT generation project with the support of the Ministry of Digital Policy of Ukraine. I have the necessary technology stack to develop modern applications and user interfaces

PROJECTS





• Social Network. React App with server & database

technologies React - ReduxToolkit - Formic - RouterDom - Material UI -

WebSocket - MongoDB - Express - Trello

https://github.com/AlexHiriavenko/social-network/tree/develop source https://fs-social-network.netlify.app/ website for logIn check Link

• Privilege Handmade. React app. Online Store.

React - Redux - Formic - RouterDom ContextApi - Tests technologies source https://github.com/AlexHiriavenko/onlineStore-HandMade

website https://privilege-handmade.netlify.app/

Medical Portal

technologies JS classes, Fetch API, Bootstrap, Responsive design, Gulp

source https://github.com/AlexHiriavenko/medical-portal

website https://medical-portal.netlify.app/ for logIn check Link

Brooklyn Library

JavaScript, CSS. (auth, slider, tabs, user profile, store, etc) technologies

source Github

Library project link website

EXPERIENCE

FRONT END DEVELOPER INTERNSHIP

DAN.IT

10.2022 - 09.2023

Four modules completed during the year. Successfully completed five projects (all scores above 90%) using the stack of technologies mentioned above. Gained experience of working in a team (2, 3, 9 people). In one of the projects, I served as a team lead.

- HTML, CSS & JavaScript
- Advanced: HTML, CSS, SCSS. Responsive design.
- Advanced JavaScript, testing, Bootstrap
- React & Redux(thunk, toolkit), routing, Formik, MUI, testing,
- Introduction to Node.js, Express & Mongo DB

PREVIOUS EXPERIENCE

PURCHASING MANAGER

VHH Group 2019 - present

Provision of production with the necessary equipment, components, tools, materials

CATEGORY PURCHASING MANAGER

LLC "Effect"

Purchase of goods, increased sales, and improved turnover of inventory.

SALES AND MARKETING SPECIALIST

Amstor Retail Group

Product promotion and sales increase